

Phùng Thế Anh

Frontend Developer

- phungtheanh2001@gmail.com \$\ 0386136374
- O Cau Giay, Ha Noi

- 5 05/10/2001
- https://phungtheanh.github.io/Portfolio/

PROFILE

I have 2 years experience and many clients are happy with the projects carried out As a person with good logical thinking and creative ability, I hope to become one of the company's key programmers to bring optimal technology solutions to customers. At the same time, I want to improve my professional qualifications and career capacity

- · Active, enthusiastic, honest, careful
- analyze, evaluate, solve problems, find solutions, make decisions, work in groups, communicate well

SKILLS

HTML • CSS • Sass • Bootstrap • Tailwind • Wordpress • Javascript •

ElectronJs • ReactJs • Nextjs • Typescript • React Native • Github •

RESTful api

ENGLISH

Listen Speak Read Write

EDUCATION

Electric Power University (8/2019 - 5/2024)

Information technology major

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Aneed joint stock company, Frontend

06/2022 - 01/2024 Frontend Developer

Vietcas Company, Frontend

03/2024 - present | Ha Noi, Việt Nam

Website about courses

08/2022 - 12/2022

Role: Frontend (Nextjs)

- Cut and complete the website interface according to Figma design
- Combine with BE to combine API for website
- Edit website interface according to customer requirements

Website about global import and export

02/2023 - 06/2023

Role: Frontend (NextJs)

- Cut and complete the website interface according to Figma
- Combine with BE to combine API for website
- Combine with BA and Tester to edit website according to design
- Edit website interface according to customer requirements

Website about company

08/2023 - 11/2023

Role: Frontend (NextJs) and Backend(Wordpress)

- Cut and complete the website interface according to Figma design
- Combine with BE by Wordpress to combine API for website
- Edit website interface according to tester requirements